Bob Bullock Campaigns papers, Inclusive: 1970-1996, Bulk: 1973-1996
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 1994 Campaign, 1991-1995; 6
  - Mosbacher, 1991-1994; 9
    - News Clippings, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Notebooks, 1990-1992; 10
    - 1994 Senate Race Analysis-Primary and General Elections, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Polls, 1991-1994; 11
    - Bennett, Petts & Associates, 1992 August-September (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Carriker Poll, 1994 August (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Clippings, 1991 July (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1993 February (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Dallas Morning News /UTD Poll of Legislators, 1991 August 26 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Election Results, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - General Information, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Johnson Senate Seat Poll Summary, 1991 October (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Krueger Poll-Public Strategies, 1993 February 17 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Likely Voters for Lt. Governor’s Race-Texas Poll, 1994 October (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Mason Dixon Texas Poll-Survey Report, 1994 July, November (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Montford Poll, 1994 October (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - MSI Statewide Poll, 1994 August 2-5 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - National Survey of American Adults and Their Attitudes Toward Legalized Gambling-Fabrizio, McLaughlin & Ass., 1994 July 15 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Phone Survey for Texas Unity ’92, Tabular Report (1 of 6), 1992 September (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Phone Survey for Texas Unity ’92, Tabular Report (2 of 6), 1992 September (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Phone Survey for Texas Unity ’92, Tabular Report (3 of 6), 1992 September (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Phone Survey for Texas Unity ’92, Tabular Report (4 of 6), 1992 September (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Phone Survey for Texas Unity ’92, Tabular Report (5 of 6), 1992 September (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Phone Survey for Texas Unity ’92, Tabular Report (6 of 6), 1992 September (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Ratliff Poll, 1994 July (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - School Finance Poll-A Survey of Public Attitudes, Shipley & Associates, 1992 March (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - School Finance Poll-Shipley & Associates, 1992 March; undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - School Finance Poll-Shipley & Associates, 1992 March; undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Senate District 1 Poll-Bullock Favorability, 1992 June (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Sibley Poll, 1994 August (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Sibley Poll, 1994 October (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Sims Poll, 1994 June (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Sims Poll, 1994 October (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Southwest Voter Research Institute-Report on the 1992 Election Studies, 1993 January 14 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - State Senate District 2, 1992 July (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - State Senate District 6, 1994 Democratic Primary-Benchmark Survey-TEXPAC (1 of 5), 1993 November (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - State Senate District 6, 1994 Democratic Primary-Benchmark Survey-TEXPAC (2 of 5), 1993 November (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - State Senate District 6, 1994 Democratic Primary-Benchmark Survey-TEXPAC (3 of 5), 1993 November (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - State Senate District 6, 1994 Democratic Primary-Benchmark Survey-TEXPAC (4 of 5), 1993 November (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - State Senate District 6, 1994 Democratic Primary-Benchmark Survey-TEXPAC (5 of 5), 1993 November (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - State Senate Election Analysis, 1993 February 16 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Statewide-Hickman/Brown Poll, 1994 July (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Statewide Public Opinion Survey IV-The Eppstein Group, 1993 April (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Statewide Survey Executive Summary Report for TMA & TTLA, Shipley & Associates (1 of 2), 1991 July (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Statewide Survey Executive Summary Report for TMA & TTLA, Shipley & Associates (2 of 2), 1991 July (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Survey of Public Attitudes in the State of Texas-Shipley & Associates, 1991 July (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Survey of Public Attitudes in the State of Texas-Shipley & Associates, 1993 September (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Survey of Public Attitudes in the State of Texas-Shipley & Associates, 1994 September (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Survey on Public Policy Opinion in Texas on Legal Issues-Texas Public Policy Foundation, 1991 February (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Survey of Registered Voters-Senatorial District 22 and McLennan County, 1991 October (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Survey of State District 4- Senator Carl Parker, Delta Research )1 of 3), 1991 June (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Survey of State District 4- Senator Carl Parker, Delta Research (2 of 3), 1991 June (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Survey of State District 4- Senator Carl Parker, Delta Research (3 of 3), 1991 June (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Texas 23rd Senate District-Survey of Public Attitudes, Shipley & Associates, 1991 September (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Texas Income Tax-Greenberg-Lake, 1991 April (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Texas Interested Citizens-The Eppstein Group, 1991 July (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Texas Interested Citizens Statewide Public Opinion Survey-The Eppstein Group, 1994 August 25-September 2 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Texas Poll, 1992 Spring (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Texas Poll-Educational Economics Policy Center Survey, 1993 September 22 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1991 May (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1991 August (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1992 May (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Texas Statewide Survey, 1991 July 8 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Tracking Poll-Emory, Young & Associates, 1994 October (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Senate Race- The Texas Poll, 1993 February (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Zaffirini Poll, 1994 October (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Position Papers, 1992-1994; 12
    - Bullock ’94 News and Information Packet, circa 1994 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Crime and Drugs, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Publications, 1992-1994; 13
    The Publications subseries has four sub-subseries: Articles, News clippings, Newsletters, and Press Releases. Publicity covers various forms of public media which Bullock collected or people sent him about himself, his campaigns and politics in general. The various forms of publications are arranged chronologically.
    - Articles, 1993-1994; 1
      - General, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - General, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - News Clippings, 1992; 2
      - General, 1992 May (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - General, 1992 September (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - General, 1992 December (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Newsletters, 1992-1994; 3
      - The Bullock Update, Campaign Newsletter, Fall, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Bullock ‘94, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Press Releases, 1992-1994; 4
      - General, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - General, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - General, 1994 February (Box 48, Folder 25)
      - General, 1994 March (Box 48, Folder 26)
      - General, 1994 April (Box 48, Folder 27)
      - General, 1994 May (Box 48, Folder 28)
      - General, 1994 June (Box 48, Folder 29)
      - General, 1994 August (Box 48, Folder 30)
      - General, 1994 September (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - General, 1994 October (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Reports, 1992-1994; 14
    - Issues for Texans Now, 1992 October (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - The Senate Side-A Report on the 73rd Legislature to Texas Business, Industry and Commerce, circa 1994 (Box 48, Folder 34)
- Post-1995 Campaign, 1995-1996; 7
  The Post 1995 Campaign series contains four subseries: Campaign Materials, Invitations — Fundraisers, Polls, and Publications — Newsletters.
  The Post 1995 Campaign Materials contains materials used in political campaigns, such as banners and apparel. Invitations — Fundraisers reflect fundraising and campaign events for Bullock and other politicians. The Polls subseries contains information on election surveys, public attitude surveys, telephone surveys, and polling reports. Publications — Newsletters contains two volumes of Texas News and Views about the political climate and events surrounding Bullock’s political campaigns.
  - Campaign Materials, 1996, undated; 1
    - Banners, “Bob Bullock”, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Banners, “Bob Bullock Lt. Governor”, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Banners, “Bob Bullock Lt. Governor”, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Banners, “Bob Bullock For Lt. Governor”, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Banners, “God Bless Texas”, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Banners, “The Best is Yet To Come”, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Hat, “Bob Bullock” on black baseball cap, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Pen set, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - T-shirt, “Clearly the Best, Bob Bullock, Lt. Governor”, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Invitations - Fundraisers, 1995-1996; 2
    - Four Seasons Hotel, 1996 September 26 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - “Say Yes to Texas, Say Yes to Bullock”, 1995 October 19 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Polls, 1995-1996; 3
    - El Paso Poll, 1995 April (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Garry Mauro-White House Bulletin, 1996 August 6 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - “How Texans Stand on Key Issues”- The Texas Poll, 1995 February (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - “How Texans Like the New Governor & Four Key Issues That Divided the Candidates”- The Texas Poll, 1995 February (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - NAACP Statewide Poll, pgs. 1-59, 1995 February (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - NAACP Statewide Poll, pgs. 60-136, 1995 February (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - National Poll-Public Opinion Toward Entitlements and Federal Deficit-Hamilton & Staff, 1995 June (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Phil Gramm Poll, circa 1995 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Previous Poll List, Shipley & Associates, 1995 June 28 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Public Attitudes and Open-Ended Responses, Shipley & Associates, 1995 June-July (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Public Strategies, Inc., 1996 August (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Puder Consulting, circa 1996 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Rhodes Poll-Shipley & Associates, 1996 October (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - State House District 47 GOP Primary Benchmark Survey-The Eppstein Group, 1995 October 2-4 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Statewide Public Opinion Survey-The Eppstein Group, 1995 November (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Tarrance Group-Texas For Judicial Election Reform, 1995 March (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Texas Interested Citizens Statewide Public Opinion Poll-The Eppstein Group, 1995 April 14-21 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Texas Poll-Affirmative Action, 1995 April 26 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Texas Public Policy Foundation, 1996 Spring (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Texas State Senate District #24 Polling Summary-Shipley & Associates, 1996 July (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Texas State Senate District #24 Tracker Poll-Shipley & Associates, 1996 October 17 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Texas Statewide Survey- Shipley & Associates, 1995 June (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Texas Statewide Survey-Project 248014, Shipley & Associates, 1995 June (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Texas Statewide Survey Results-Public Opinion Strategies, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Texas Victory Democrats Political Poll, Mark Mellman, 1996 September 25 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Publications - Newsletters, 1996; 4
    - Texas News and Views, Vol. No. 1, 1996 Spring (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Texas News and Views, Vol. No. 2, 1996 Spring (Box 49, Folder 38)